# Santiago Landaburo

I am a 24-year-old Information Systems Analyst, currently in my final year of a degree program in the same field. I am a curious person who is passionate about programming and constantly seeking new knowledge. I have a great ability to immerse myself in situations, which allows me to find creative and effective solutions to the challenges that arise. With problem-solving and critical thinking skills, I always strive to exceed my own limits and tackle new challenges.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FCYT - UADER, Concepción del Uruguay - Teaching Assistant

March 2023 - Present

 At the beginning of the 2023 academic year, I started as a Teaching Assistant for Algorithms and Data Structures in the Information Systems degree program.

### Bombieri, Concepción del Uruguay — Frontend Jr. Adv. Developer

June 2021 - Present

- I focused on frontend development by taking an advanced React course, which helped me get promoted.
- I participated in the analysis and design stage in some projects.
- I started as a junior developer in Javascript, performing frontend and backend tasks.

# Rebrit, Gualeguaychú – Web developer

March 2021 - June 2021

- My activities involved layout design and integrating screens with the PHP backend.
- It was my first experience as a professional programmer.

#### **EDUCATION**

# FCYT - UADER, Concepción del Uruguay - Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems

January 2018 - PRESENT, Concepción del Uruguay.

I am currently in my final year of the degree program.

# FCYT - UADER, Concepción del Uruguay - Information Systems Analyst

January 2018 - May DEL 2022, Concepción del Uruguay

In May 2022, I obtained my degree as an Information Systems Analyst by defending a final project that involved the complete development of an e-commerce platform.

# EET N° 2 "Pbro. Jose Maria Colombo", Gualeguaychú — Computer Technician.

January 2011 - December 2017, Gualeguaychú

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Advanced React course on Udemy

Completion of several personal projects prior to my first job.